Hi, um, I'm just sorry for the messy background.
I did not set up yet because I'm quite busy and moving around
to the next house we're gonna do.
But, bit of a, uh, give me morning,
and my name is Fritz Arrobrina, and I'm from Calendora City,
Philippines, so I am applying for the video editor position because content
creation and video editing are errors that I genuinely
enjoy and continuously improve.
You want. And I have experience creating short,
uh, form videos, uh,
social media, content, uh,
branding materials, and engagement management focus edits for platforms
like Facebook, Instagram,
TikTok. And Reels, as well. And I mainly use CopCut,
uh, Canva, and other creative tools for editing.
Uh, my editing experience includes transitions,
captions, audio syncs,
uh, visual effects, emotion-based- elements,
uh, branding valid, uh, visuals, and optimizing videos for mobile-first
of viewing and audience engagement as well.
And I enjoy creating fast-paced and visually engaging edits that
o- or decide to capture attentions quickly.
And especially for short-form social media content and advertisement.
And that's what I'm working on right now as a social media manager.
And I also like, experimenting with- hooks of facing and
storytelling styles to improve, uhh,
attentions and, uhh, engagement.
So aside from editing skills, uhh,
I also have compatible working remotely.
And collaborate- with teams, uh,
handling multiple projects, and adapting to feedback,
uhh, professionally. And I'm organized,
a detail-oriented, and always willing to learn new editing styles,
uhh, tools and creative strategies. So what's- to me.
Make me strong, fit for it as a rule, as my creativity,
and adaptability, a strong work ethic,
and a passion for creating engagement content that performs well online.
And I genuinely enjoy improving my skills,
and, uh, finding ways to make every project better than the
last one. So, uh,
ever, you want more information, uh,
from my, uh, editing skills, I have all of my,
uh, youth of, a video,
because I like supporting for those music,
uh, rap artists. So,
I do editing for the music video they have.
And once again, thank you very much for your time,
and I look forward to the opportunity you'll purchase. And maybe to work with
your team. Bye bye. Bye.